welcome back to another audacity
欢迎回到另一个大胆的地方
tutorial in this video I'm going to show
在这段视频中 我将展示教程
you how to record the sound from your
您如何录制声音从您的
computer so if you're playing music on
所以如果你在电脑上播放音乐
your computer you're watching something
你的电脑你在看什么
online on Netflix or on YouTube you can
在Netflix或YouTube上 您可以
actually capture that audio that's
实际上捕捉到的音频是
coming out of your computer playing
从你的电脑里出来玩
through your speakers or on your
通过扬声器或通过您的
headphones so basically anything on your
所以基本上你耳机上的任何东西
speakers you can record an audacity to
您可以大胆录制的扬声器
do that though you'll notice under the
这样做 尽管您会注意到在
microphone we have to change so that
我们必须更换麦克风 这样才能
we're listening to our audio card on our
我们正在收听我们的声卡
computer and not listening to the
计算机 而不是监听
microphone so right now if I hit record
麦克风所以现在如果我按下唱片
I'm recording from my microphone only
我只用我的麦克风录音
and if we come here to audio file under
如果我们来到这里的音频文件下
music I have like this audio file it's a
音乐我喜欢这个音频文件它是一个
MIDI so we can hear it but if we hit
所以我们可以听到 但是如果我们击中了
record it didn't if we hit record now if
如果我们现在点击记录 就不会记录
we play this back but if we hit record
我们回放这段视频 但如果我们打出了唱片
see it didn't catch the audio from the
看 它没有捕捉到来自
speaker's even though you heard it in my
扬声器的声音 即使你在我的
in this tutorial we didn't capture it on
在本教程中 我们没有捕捉到
audacity so to change that what we need
如此大胆地改变我们所需要的
to do let's just go file new let's bring
要做的事 让我们去归档新的 我们带来
up a whole brand new window we go to
打开一个全新的窗口 我们要去
edit we go to preferences and under this
编辑我们转到首选项 然后在此
host yours might be different and in
托管您的主机可能不同 并且在
fact this these instructions will
事实上 这些指示将
probably only work on windows now that I
可能只在Windows上工作 因为我
think about it but we need to change our
想想看 但我们需要改变我们的
host to this wasa API windows so if we
主机是一个API窗口 所以如果我们
change that in here then under recording
在这里更改 然后在录音下
we get some different options we still
我们仍然有一些不同的选择
have our microphone but we also have
有我们的麦克风 但我们也有
this speakers we have a loopback I have
这个扬声器 我们有一个环回
2 X 2 I have one for my rode microphone
2X2我有一个用于我的骑马麦克风
but I just have this regular speaker
但我只有一个普通的演讲者
slash headphone and it's my real Tech
斜杠耳机 这是我真正的技术
audio so real Tech's a common audio
音频 真正的技术是一种常见的音频
interface so I'm gonna select this and
界面 所以我将选择此选项并
now when I say ok now when I record
现在当我说好的时候 当我录音的时候
first of all if I hit record right now
首先 如果我现在创了纪录
testing testing 1 2 3
测试测试%1%2%3
nothing's happening if we hit stop it
如果我们按下停止键什么都不会发生
doesn't record anything at all because
根本不录制任何东西 因为
there's nothing playing there's no input
没有播放任何东西 没有输入
at all on this these speakers and
在这方面 这些演讲者和
headphones but now if I go and actually
但现在如果我走了 实际上
play some audio
播放一些音频
so now we actually have this it was
所以现在我们有了这个 它是
there we go
好了 我们走吧
so now we actually have this audio that
所以现在我们实际上有这段音频
we've captured and we can play it in
我们已经俘获了 我们可以在其中发挥作用
audacity so we can let's see yeah
大胆 所以我们可以看看是的
so let's hit play here okay there was a
所以让我们在这里点击Play 好的 有一个
little bit of a hiccup on capturing that
在捕捉到这一点上有一点小问题
so this is actually doing a lot of
所以这实际上是在做很多事情
interesting things this is playback this
有趣的事情这是回放这是
is a MIDI file being played back and
是否正在播放MIDI文件 并且
then we're recording it so actually it's
然后我们正在录制它 所以实际上它是
actually stepping through a whole bunch
实际上穿过了一大堆
of different audio settings on the
上的不同音频设置
computer the different audio processes
计算不同的音频过程
but there you have it and we can do the
但现在你有了它 我们可以做
same thing if I come to the end of this
如果我走到这一步 也一样
we want to go we just hit let's play a
我们想去 我们只需敲击 让我们玩一把
YouTube video here like there's one of
YouTube上的视频看起来就像是
my youtube videos and hit record so it's
我的YouTube视频和热门唱片 所以它
actually recording what's happening on
实际上记录了发生了什么
the video here and then we can close
视频在这里 然后我们就可以结束了
this hit stop here and we see it's
这辆车停在这里 我们看到它是
actually recorded this different audio
实际上录制了这段不同的音频
so we just we just recorded audio from a
所以我们只是我们刚刚录制了一段音频
YouTube video and from a MIDI file being
YouTube视频和从MIDI文件
playback on our computer so that's how
在我们的计算机上回放 这就是为什么
you would do that and so just make sure
你会这么做的 所以你要确保
you can change this and if you don't
你可以改变这一点 如果你不改变
have an option to record from your
可以选择从您的
speakers or headphone or sometimes it's
扬声器或耳机 或者有时
called the name of your audio interface
调用您的音频接口的名称
then just go to edit preferences and you
然后只需转到编辑首选项 您就可以
might need to change your host to
可能需要将您的主机更改为
something different and I'm on Linux and
一些不同的东西 我在Linux上
Mac I think on Linux you can use do it
Mac我认为在Linux上可以使用Do It
by default at least on depending on your
默认情况下 至少取决于您的
what distribution you're using on Mac
您在Mac上使用的是什么发行版
I'm not exactly sure I'm going to change
我不太确定我会不会改变
mine back here but yeah that's how you
我的在这里 但是的 这就是你
do it
去做吧
I guess one more thing I'll say if you
我想我还有一件事要说 如果你
need to if they're still not working you
如果他们还是不让你工作 就需要
can always right-click down here where
可以始终在此处单击鼠标右键
you adjust your volume you can right
你可以调节你的音量
click and then you can go to open sound
点击即可打开音效
settings and you might have some
设置 你可能有一些
different options you can play around
你可以玩的不同选择
with in here as well to choose like your
在这里也可以选择像你
your to father if you're if you're still
如果你还在
not able to record you might just need
无法记录你可能只需要
to go into your sound setting this is
为了进入你的声音设置
what I'm saying and you can maybe play
我说的话 你也许可以
around with changing different things
改变不同的事物
there to see if you can get it to work
看看你能不能把它修好
so I hope you found this video
所以我希望你找到了这段视频
informative go ahead and like comments
信息继续前进 喜欢评论
scribe and I hope to see you in the next
我希望下次能见到你
video
视频